Well, we're back for another YouTube video here in
the self-driving Tesla. I have not made a couple
of these in here. I find I can flow better when
I'm inside the Tesla. I want to talk about what's
keeping you from getting sales in your business
and then kind of the fivestep framework that I
have for making sure that you communicate the
value of your offer in your marketing in a way
that's going to get sales. Sales is the ultimate
thing that we're going after. That's what we
want. That's the most important factor that we're
getting in our business. And so the reason why I
see so many coaches, they have great offers,
they have great strategies, they have great
ways of impacting people, not getting the kind of
sales that they want. Simply is because they're
not doing enough marketing. Okay? They might think
they're posting on social media. They might say,
"Well, I'm I'm sharing once a day what I'm doing."
But here's the problem. They're not doing the
right marketing. What is the right marketing? The
right marketing is what's going to reach people
to become prospects and sales in your business.
And so what that means is having webinars, having
ebooks, having downloads, having things that
generate leads, having things that people actually
have to sign up for on your website, whether
they're purchasing it for $5. We're finding that
strategy is working really well. $5 purchase, $10
purchase. But the free lead magnet process is also
not dead. It still works. It's just that if you're
going to run ads specifically, running ads to
something that's free is going to attract people
that are not necessarily going to spend money with
you. But if you run ads to something with people
that are spending money, you'll get about 20 to
30% of those people ascending or upgrading to
your paid offer afterwards. And so that's one of
the biggest things is that I see so many coaches
spending time on what they're building. What is
the offer? What is the course? what's inside of
it that I'm sharing with people and not as much
time on actually attracting buyers to them. Now,
the five-step framework for attracting buyers,
I got it printed out right here. This is why I
love the self-driving car because I can have my
print out right here in front of me. Is stage
number one, and this is where most coaches,
they kind of fall off, is you lead with logic.
What are the features? I'm tired. I need energy.
This is commoditized language. This is what
everybody leads with. This is not unique. This
is not going to make you stand out. This is not
going to connect with somebody to get them to buy
from you. So, we got to go five layers deep on
this one. Layer two is consequences. Okay. So,
let's say somebody is tired and they
need energy. Let's we're going to go
from that strategy. That's that's what I got
written down right here. Consequences. They're
falling behind on work. They're snapping at
their family. They're irritable. Okay. So,
now that's dutybased. This is the duty that
they have to their workplace, to their family,
how they need to start showing up differently in
the world. And so when you write your sales copy,
when you create content that leads from that
place, it starts to personalize it better for
people. But we need to go a step further here.
Identity based. Maybe I'm not the kind of person
that can do this, that can have their energy be
that way. meaning that they're starting to think,
you want them to start to think more emotionally
of, wow, what if I'm not the kind of person that
has enough energy and what needs to turn me into
this? So that they start experiencing that like,
okay, what needs to change in my identity to
start showing up as a person with more energy.
So they're not self-identifying with their fatigue
or their lack of energy or things like that.
Now number four and this is the big part. Secret
emotions, resentment, guilt, feeling trapped. What
is the pain that they would never say out loud
that they keep secret that they don't talk to
other people about? What keeps them up at night?
You know, we have a process that we go through,
one of my favorite books on this. It's called
the ultimate salesletter, uh, version 4 by Dan
Kennedy, and it has a whole thing called the
10 smart market diagnosis questions. We run
this through AI, our AI agents, and we have them
come up with a framework to write our sales copy.
And it's baked in there to have this. And one of
the biggest things that you want is you want to
figure out what are those secret emotions. What
keeps them up at night? What keeps them boiling
up to their ears with frustration? What do they
resent? What do they feel guilty about? What do
they feel trapped in? that they can't get out
of the pain that they won't tell other people
about because they feel embarrassed about it. Now
all of those things are great but they don't lead
to the sale. Those are leading to the layer number
five and that is where the hero where the prospect
becomes the hero and the hero returns where you
become the powerful version of yourself. And this
is what people pay for. People are willing to pay
for the ability to go from not just stress relief,
not just having more energy, not just showing
up as the better version of themselves,
but moving past the guilt, past the shame to
becoming the ultimate superhero version of
yourself. And so when you're creating an offer in
your business and you're marketing it and you're
and you're showing people how to do the thing that
you do, you help them go from simply just okay,
you're going to have more energy. You're going to
have less stress. You're not you're not going to
be kept awake at night. You're going to you're
going to feel better. We're going to go out of
that commoditized language of logic, out of the
just so, you know, you're going to stop falling
behind, out of the identity statement,
out of the secret frustrations, and into
the powerful superhero version of themselves
that they have always dreamed of being. And
that's what people will pay for. They will pay
for a transformation that takes them from where
they are feeling like they're falling behind,
feeling like they're not the type of person who
does the things that they want to do to changing
and transforming out of the chrysalis like the
butterfly coming out, the caterpillar that goes
in and turns into this beautiful butterfly.
When somebody can see themselves in your
sales copy, in your offer, in your language,
in what you're doing, and even right now as I'm
talking about this video, you're imagining how
you would change your sales copy to do this.
And and by the way, you could literally take
this framework. You could take this video right
here. I actually want to encourage you on this.
Try try this out. Take this video right here that
I just talked about the the link in YouTube. Copy
it into an AI agent or Google Gemini. Gemini
is really good because it's connected right to
YouTube. Paste your current sales copy and your
offer into it. Take this video and tell Gemini,
I want you to remake and rewrite my entire offer
based on the strategies in this video. I'm telling
you, the AI inside of Gemini knows how to do
this really well. And all other agents are going
to learn how to do this pretty soon. All other AI
tools like chat, GPT, and all of that. and it will
then rewrite and recreate your offer based on what
I just shared about in this video. And you are
going to be blown away the different perspective
that it's going to take. When you take your offer
and you go beyond just the commoditized version
of it, what is the what are the pieces that you're
selling? What are those things that that you're
that you're giving to people? What are the five
videos that you're sharing? And it turns into a
vehicle. I'm in a vehicle right now. I'm in an
artificial intelligence vehicle. This has AI in it
that's driving the vehicle while I'm driving. And
I go from point A to point B. It's a vehicle from
getting me from where I am to where I want to be.
When your offer becomes a vehicle of transforming
people from a caterpillar to a butterfly,
the superhero version of themselves, and they
can clearly see it. They can clearly see it in
the sales copy. They can clearly read it. They
can tell that that is what you're delivering.
People will spend good money to work with you and
to become your client. My friends, I'm actually
excited. I'm going to take this video myself and
I'm going to have my AI literally take this and
restructure some of my offers through this type
of concept, you know, not just like write it
into like some like comic book type of thing. And
and since we're having our AI do this, you know,
let's instruct it as the AI reads this. We're
not turning this into some sort of of confusing,
unbelievable, or boring version of Remember
that's the Cub score right there, CUB. We don't
want it to be confusing. We don't want it to be
unbelievable. We don't want it to be boring. Most
of us are writing boring sales copy, but we don't
want it to be confusing or unbelievable. We want
it to be reasonable, realistic, but it taps into
those emotional drivers that get people to go from
just our our vanilla offer to that transformative
hero version, and that's what produces sales for
you in your business. I'm excited to see what
comes out of this. I'm excited to to literally
just copy and paste my own video right into
my offers and see what this produces. And I
want to see in the comments below, I want this
to be interactive. I want you to share with me
some of the outputs that you got from doing this
in your own business. We'll talk soon everybody.